# Dictionary with all the questions
# and their relevant answers

quiz = {
    1: {
        "question": "\nQ1: The Maori word for 'five'",
        "answer": "Rima"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "\nQ2: Christchurch's Maori name?",
        "answer": "Otautahi"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "\nQ3: Maori word for 'chicken'",
        "answer": "Heihei"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "\nQ4: Count to ten in Maori",
        "answer": "tahi rua toru wha rima ono whitu waru iwa tekau"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "\nQ5: Translate 'rƒÅtapu' into english",
        "answer": "Sunday"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "\nQ6: Translate 'rua tekau' into English (Use letters)",
        "answer": "Twenty"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "\nQ7: Translate whanau into English",
        "answer": "Family"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "\nQ8: Translate 'New Zealand' into Maori",
        "answer": "Aotearoa"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "\nQ9: Maori for 'Ocean'",
        "answer": "Moana"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "\nQ10: 'One hundred' in Maori?",
        "answer": "Kotahi rau"
    }}
